(soothing music)
In this section, we will take a look
behind the scenes of JavaScript
and learn how the language actually works.
So, throughout this section,
we will take your basic knowledge of JavaScript
and elevate it to a completely new level
where you will then understand exactly how everything
that you learned before actually works under the hood.
And this is actually extremely important
because this knowledge will really empower you
to write better code and to understand
other developer's code
and so in the end, it will make you a better,
more confident and more successful developer.
Now, I'm telling you all this
because some people find this kind of theory lectures boring
for some reason, but they are really not.
And I actually invested well over a month
into building this section alone.
And so that might show you
just how crucial this information is.
And finally, knowing how JavaScript really works
will also set you apart from the competition
because many other junior developers simply don't know
about much of this stuff.
So, don't be scared of theory and let's get started.
(upbeat music)